{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Aluminum \u0026 Metal Siding Repair Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40145/":{"taskOID":40145,"originalTaskOID":40145,"setID":456,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":1071,"questionDisplayText":"Visible Symptoms","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"List any visible symptoms.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3501,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Leak through the wall or into the basement","answerDisplayText":"Leak through the wall or into the basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5692,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Siding panel is loose or hanging out of position","answerDisplayText":"Siding panel is loose or hanging out of position","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5691,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Siding panel is has blown off","answerDisplayText":"Siding panel is has blown off","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5687,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Siding is dented","answerDisplayText":"Siding is dented","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5683,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Siding color has faded","answerDisplayText":"Siding color has faded","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1483,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Color is blistering/peeling","answerDisplayText":"Color is blistering/peeling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4073,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Need repair/replacement of soffits, fascia or other trim","answerDisplayText":"Need repair/replacement of soffits, fascia or other trim","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":1071,"questionDisplayText":"Visible Symptoms","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"List any visible symptoms.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3501,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Leak through the wall or into the basement","answerDisplayText":"Leak through the wall or into the basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5692,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Siding panel is loose or hanging out of position","answerDisplayText":"Siding panel is loose or hanging out of position","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5691,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Siding panel is has blown off","answerDisplayText":"Siding panel is has blown off","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5687,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Siding is dented","answerDisplayText":"Siding is dented","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5683,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Siding color has faded","answerDisplayText":"Siding color has faded","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1483,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Color is blistering/peeling","answerDisplayText":"Color is blistering/peeling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4073,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Need repair/replacement of soffits, fascia or other trim","answerDisplayText":"Need repair/replacement of soffits, fascia or other trim","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3501,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Leak through the wall or into the basement","answerDisplayText":"Leak through the wall or into the basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5692,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Siding panel is loose or hanging out of position","answerDisplayText":"Siding panel is loose or hanging out of position","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5691,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Siding panel is has blown off","answerDisplayText":"Siding panel is has blown off","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5687,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Siding is dented","answerDisplayText":"Siding is dented","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5683,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Siding color has faded","answerDisplayText":"Siding color has faded","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1483,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Color is blistering/peeling","answerDisplayText":"Color is blistering/peeling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4073,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Need repair/replacement of soffits, fascia or other trim","answerDisplayText":"Need repair/replacement of soffits, fascia or other trim","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","__cache./api/resource/task/40145/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40145,"taskName":"Metal Siding: Repair or Partially Replace","taskDescription":"Repair or Partially Replace Metal Siding","xmTaskDescriptor":"Aluminum \u0026 Metal Siding Repair Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":220,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Metal aluminum material roofing replacement","textMessagingName":"Repr Metal Side","rolloverLongDesc":"Includes steel \u0026 aluminum siding. Some newer types are metal with a vinyl skin. This category also includes repairing coverings on trim areas, gutter boards \u0026 overhangs. Note separate categories for vinyl \u0026 for installation.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes steel, aluminum. Some coated with vinyl.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair or Partially Replace Metal Siding.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Aluminum Siding Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Fix Metal or Steel Siding","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":69,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Metal Siding Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Metal Siding: Repair or Partially Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Metal Siding Project","urlName":"Metal-Siding-Repair-or-Partially-Replace","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Aluminum Siding Repair Contractors - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Metal \u0026 Steel Siding Repair","searchKeywords":"Metal,aluminum,material,roofing,replacement,steel,exterior,concrete,stone,world,Partially,Siding","emcCategoryOid":-12064,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":456,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}